<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Culture Shock</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_law">Law</string>
    <string name="title_culture">Culture</string>
    <string name="title_phrases">Phrases</string>
    <string name="title_feed">Feed</string>

    <string name="lawText">

        •  Drinking Age 21\n
        •  Weed is legal in only some states, check the specific state for regulations\n
        •  Alcoholic Beverages can’t be in public\n
        •  Driving on the right side of the road\n
        •  Different states have different laws\n
        •  Jaywalking is illegal\n
        •  Smoking is against the law in most public places\n
        •  Sometimes public spaces will have designated smoking areas\n

    </string>

    <string name="phraseText">

        Where is the…? \n
        Can I have water? \n
        I would like to order this. \n
        Thank you, you\'re welcome. \n
        Excuse me. \n
        I\'m sorry. \n
        Yes please. \n
        Sir/Ma\'am. \n

    </string>

    <string name="foodText">

        • Tipping culture: At the end of meals customers are expected to tip their waiter.\n
        • 15% = General Minimum/Satisfied\n
        • 18% = Very Satisfied\n
        • 20+%= Great Service!\n
        • When you go to restaurants it is not uncommon to not have specific ingredients in your dish, it is ok to ask the waiter to withhold these ingredients.\n

        • In the U.S fork, knives and spoon are the customary utensils. It’s a good idea to learn other manners associated with these utensils.\n
        • Slurping, and Burping during meals is frowned upon.\n
        • While with friends, you will most likely split the bill. Generally the times when only one person pays for the bill is for special occasions, or if they insist.


    </string>


    <string name="behaviorsText">

        • It is frowned upon to spit on the ground\n
        • Direct eye contact is okay and sometimes encouraged, just don’t stare too hard\n
        • Gift giving is not common when someone invites you to their home unless it is some sort of special event, then a small gift such as wine is acceptable.\n
        • Being on time and/or early is very important in american culture\n

    </string>

    <string name="regDiffText">

        • In the south people are more likely to go out of their way to hold doors for people.\n
        • Different parts of the U.S have vastly different slang words\n
        • Tap water tastes different between states\n
        • Tap water is free in restaurants!\n
        • Since there is a drought in california you have to ask for water, they don\'t just offer it to you.\n
        • It’s generally okay to walk inside people’s houses with your shoes on.\n


    </string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="tbd">TBD</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
